Guide to the Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation: files of Steve Allen, photographer M1038
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Fairchild Semiconductor Corporation: files of Steve Allen, photographer
circa 1960-1985
M1038
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
17.0 Linear feet (25 manuscript boxes, 5 cartons)
Allen, Steve
Access to Collection
The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift of the National Semiconductor Corporation to Stanford University, Special Collections in 1991.
Scope and Contents
The Steve Allen photographs of Fairchild Semiconductor contains photographs of professional photographer Steve Allen, a Fairchild Semiconductor and National Semiconductor Corporation employee from 1966 through about 1997. The collection documents executive employees, sales force, fabrication facilities, and products of Fairchild Semiconductor. The vast majority of the collection is comprised of photographs, negatives, and slides dating from 1962-1987. There is a small amount of textual material.
Historical Note
In 1957, New York based Fairchild Camera and Instrument Corporation made a historic business decision when they sponsored the formation of Fairchild Semiconductor in Palo Alto, California. A group of eight scientists and engineers involved in solid-state electronics had developed a method of mass-producing silicon transistors using a double diffusion technique and a chemical etching system called the "mesa" process. Fairchild provided the necessary backing for the group's project and the development and production of silicon diffused transistors and other semiconductor devices began. The eight scientists and engineers were Julius Blank, Victor Grinich, Jean Hoerni, Eugene Kleiner, Jay Last, Gordon Moore, Robert Noyce, and Sheldon Roberts.
Fairchild (Firm); Photography, Industrial--United States; Photography--California--San Francisco Bay Area; Semiconductor Industry--California--Santa Clara Valley (Santa Clara Valley)--History--20th century--Sources
- Various negatives (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 2 prints, 2 negs, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- S.F. and Bay Scenincs 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- South Portland, color 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Leadwire I 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Advertisements 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Diode 1964 picninc Russ Booth (Box 1, Folder 7)
- 905 wafer and pkg. on fall leaf 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Planar Process steps photo-micro of 915 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Gift FLPA-200 boxes (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 2N3638 Epoxy device 1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Epoxy unit and Chinese lettering "Little things do big things" (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 14 Lead Cerpac 1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Out-away transistor 4200 64 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Vista Productions Shots 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Three stage MOST 1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Micrologic Family & Foreign Coins 1964 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Pile Transistors & data for them 12/64 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Six Stage Register Circuit Board 1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- 2 negs. 2 prints 1 from marked negatives 8/26/96 (Riordan Order) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- 0000 and Epoxy device 6/64 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Inline lead arrangers 12-64 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Device carriers 12-64 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- TO-5 can 1964 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Universal Carrier Devices 1964 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Radar 1962-3-4 ad in Business 1964 Week (Box 2, Folder 18)
- S.F. Bay Aerial 1965 (Box 2.1, Folder 1)
- Goldeb Gate Bridge Panorama 10/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 2)
- FC&I office Sysset 10/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 3)
- Marketing Service Photo 4/66 (Box 2.1, Folder 4)
- Wafer % classification card 8-65 per Joe Rizzi (Box 2.1, Folder 5)
- visual die inspection 3-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 6)
- Wafer slicing 7/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 7)
- Ball Bonder close-up for wire company 1 mil 3/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 8)
- Header washing 3-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 9)
- R&D in line design work, R.Rice 6/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 10)
- 2 photos by Mike Bry of Sausalito (not Fairchild property-stein) (Box 2.1, Folder 11)
- Ultrasonic bonding close up 1312 6/65 (file dev. fab.) (Box 2.1, Folder 12)
- Diode brochure candids 6/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 13)
- Microwave Prod. area 2/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 14)
- Microwave trans. mfg. steps 10/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 15)
- Diffusion 3-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 16)
- evaporation 3-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 17)
- Crystal growing 1/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 18)
- R&D interiors 1965 IEEE (Box 2.1, Folder 19)
- Hot silicon ingot being drawn 5/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 20)
- Faulty Flat-pak parts for Chiu 5/65 + 6/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 21)
- Fab 4 DVM in use 3-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 22)
- Epoxy Diode final seal FC&I annual rep. 11-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 23)
- Diode brochure pix 6-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 24)
- Optical alignment jigs Fab 4 3-65 (Box 2.1, Folder 25)
- New diffusion area 5/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 26)
- Materials ovens for sale 7/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 27)
- Diode candids 8/65 (Box 2.1, Folder 28)
- I.C. Brochure Color 10/66 II (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Reliability Broch. 1966 6/66 #2 Color (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Annual Report stuff 12/66 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Extra Prints From I.C. Broch 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Halfware speed control Consumer Applications 8/66 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Color TV w/ Solid sate components, lantern slides 9/27/66 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- IF can as heat sink for TOS 6/9/66 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Reliability Broch. 1966 4x5 6/66 #1 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Numerical Character Generator Applications 6/16/66 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Pocket FM reciever Consumer Applications 5/31/66 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Acid Burns Plant Safety 6/66 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Plant Safety Devices for Fred Hopkins 6/16/66 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- 4000 Wafer Elec. Test 4/66 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- TI2n2907a&Raytheon 2n2907a 8-65 - Ken Matsuura-Appl (Box 4, Folder 1)
- - Rhotractor/Trabbucco/Appl./ 7-65 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- "Y" Parameter tester j. Murphy 5-65 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Las Vegas computer conference FSC booth 11/65 color (Fall Joint Com. Conf.) (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Cover for SPec. Prod. catalog - 7/65 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- -Industrial brochure illus. 8-65 - mickelson GEAES (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Spec Prod brochure cover 7-65 - dual 1250's (Box 4, Folder 7)
- -Telephone- copys for DeSpain 9-65 - (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Reliability Brochure I (1965?) (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Appl T.V. w/ transistors Bray 6-65 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- -Motorola 2N-3467 WAI-Mao Yu 9-65 - (appl.) (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Fairchild FETs Appl; Vellequette (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 2N 3304-TI Matsuura Appl. 9-65 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Appl. lab gen view 7/65 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Competition FET's for appl 7/65 TI. Silicon., etc. (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Honeywell power device 6/65 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- double island spec. prod compar. for Herb Woo, appl. 7/65 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Delco Capacitor board/ Ebonheoch appl. 10-65 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- 0064,1713,1718,1702 Matsuura Appl. 10-65 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- GME 20 bit shift register appl. Per Mogenson 10-65 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- UC 1146 & 1147 Grutchfield 6-65 Appl. (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Applications taps reader 12/65 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Wafer Lapping Slicing, sorting old neg 1964 file 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Crystal Growing feature L'wire good 3/66 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 2-inch ingot growing facilities for p.r. feat. 11/66 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Custom I.C. Chips for Fortune 5/66 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- I.C. Brochure Color 10/66 I (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Epoxy TO5 and TO18 assembly 6/15/66 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Computer programming Wafer fab 12/66 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Flat Pack parts Device Fab. 5/66 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- DIP-Flat Pak-TO5 Packagaing parts 5/66 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Flip Chip Die on header-in final set Die attach machine 8/11/66 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 1600 Die Attach machine 7/66 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Final seal indry box also older pix 4/14/66 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Lead bonder, Die attach, Lead weld Jigs for D.Meshaffray 2-66 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 2-inch ingots comparison w/ 1 1/4" for article 11/66 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Ultra Sonic bonding close-up TO-5 4/66 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- R&D new const. 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- SGS Milan Copy neg 7/18/66 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Epitopial Reactor const. pix 4/66 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- DIP Parts Device Fab 1966? (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Ultrasonic Bonding 996OW on DIP 8/4/66 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Ultra-sonic bonding 4/66 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Photo Device Presentation 12/67 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Devices projected on Carol for ieee comp. 2/67 Packaging (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Epoxy DIP 8/8/67 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Appliance Man' cover pix IC in front of TV, etc. 7-67 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- DIP and FLIP DIP comparison 10/26/67 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Memory Board HDP 4091, 64 word, 2 bit, TTL Dave Deandort 8/67 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Gyrator Inductive IC HT Chuna 3/23/67 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Hybrid LSI 8 9033 chips Marvin 8/67 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Microwave Transistor packages 1967 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- 703 Epoxy Packages 5-67 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Power Device Slides Dom Femling talk 2/67 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- FAIRPAK cross section block diagram of package 7/20/67 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- LSI packages 2/67 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Micro Matrix package 1/67 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- uA726 on header 1/25/67 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Capped and uncapped DIP's for agency 1/67 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Active Filter, slides No, Calif, IEEE presentation 1/67 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- I C Brochure Slides 12-7-67 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Op Amp Module for Linear promo. for mkt. 5/67 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Packages on sand pile poss. for emp. handb'k cover. 5/67 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- EE cover on LSI (3800) with Steve Allen 11/67 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Cloyd Marvin presenting check 5/10/67 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- LSI Article Electronics Mag. 1/27/67 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Financial Analysis visit to R & D 1-67 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Korem Minister Visit 3-67 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Mac Daugall photos for Electronics World article 3/16/67 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Digital Clock Appl. Tow mills 1-67 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Lead defect chart-Roger Crosby 4/67 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Frost sensor Cons. Appl. 4/67 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Dishwasher Control Bob Hood Applications 7-67 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Washing machine control Bob Hood 5/8/67 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Temperature Control for heating pad- Bob Hood 4/27/67 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Epoxy Transistor assembly steps for Gary Logan 10-67 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Misc. Diode Color (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Schweber Booth (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Acid Burn 3-67 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Busted fire hydrant 313 Fairchild dr. 7-67 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Annual Report pix 10/67 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Crystal Grow 4-67 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Wandry pic Alloy Jct. device 5/67 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- acid burned hand (Box 7, Folder 14)
- "QST" Award Sopkin 10/67 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Space pix from NASA 4/67 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Architects rendering of Schley OTS Building. 8/67 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- SGS Italy pictures from P.R. 4-67 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- SGS Italy pictures from P.R. 4-67 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Wescon 67 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Hawaii Pix Pre-sales conf. 5/6 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Misc. Manufacturing Scenes Mt. View 4-67 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- R & D Exteriors 3-67 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- South Portland Exterior Scenics. 4-67 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Judys So. Port. Interiors 6-67 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Australia Plants Morton Beebe 1967 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Australia Beebe 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- H.E.D. Diodes for icee 2/67 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 0016 Microwave Transistor 5/67 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Blant tour P.R. prepared 7-67 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- New Ellis Street Semicond Construction Pix 12-67 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- 2N2905A for contract report 4/30/68 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- 2N914 & 2N2219A for mil. qualification 2/22/1968 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Mil Qual. 2N2906-7-8 3517 10/23/68 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- 36 Lead DIP 5/2/68 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- SH 2002 plastic DIP packaging steps for DeSai 3/13/68 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- 24 Lead DIP & Flatpack for Jack Ayre 3/68 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- S-24275 Transistor Package 1/68 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Package development photos for Dave Fusaro 2/15/68 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Mil. Qualification Transistor Photos 4/18/68 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- 2N 2906 2N 2907 2N 2221 2N 2221a 10/16/68 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Blaser Paper for Chicago Show 5/15/68 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- MSA 8505 Package 7/10/68 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- EPT 100 Photo transistor 2/12/68 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- FPT 100 (Photo transistor) Maybe poor 2/6/68 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Certube Package with 737 inside 5/15/68 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Package talk slides for Gary Logan. 1/23/68 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- HDP 1000 package 2/27/68 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Machine design article Fish Eye 6/68 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- 733 in TO 5 with disc memory for J. Ayer 11-13-68 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Chicago booth 6/68 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Linear Brochure 10/68 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Regional Sales Managers Photo 7/30/68 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Hoeft Amp. 10/18/68 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Controller and Manifold Photos for Hood 9/13/68 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Frequency synthesizer John Gregory 7/26/68 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Darryl Lieux & Bob Ricks for mag. article 12/18/68 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Electronic Design magazine cover stuff 3/25/68 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Consumer App. Brochure 1/1968 (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Electron micrographs of wafer defects for Larry Johnson 5/3/68 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Photo devices for ED Mag 7/24/68 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Lead bonding for Erwin Oswald 11-14-68 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Slides of IC packages with dimensions 7/18/68 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Micro Paks in spoon 8/31/68 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Radiation Resistant Descrete device Packages... 8/28/68 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Copies of electron micrographs for Larry Johnson 6/18/68 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Hybrid Brochure 11-68 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Power devices in bin for Ciochetti by Stein 6/68 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- A&D promotion with smock girl paper negs 3/1/68 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- 4500 Design Kit for Takigawa 2/16/68 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Promotional item memo for Rich Wills 2/26/68 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Photos for Management Course Mailer #1 Walther with $ 11-5-68 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Re-do of Annual Report cover 2/68 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Chicago Spring Conference 5/68 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Tie tack mailer 5/13/68 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Certub Package & Socket 5/2/68 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- MICRO PAK miniature trans. 5/68 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Annual Report photos 1968 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Packaging shots for Dave Fusaro 6/18/68 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- MSA 7505 Package 7/10/68 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- SAM/RAM 10/68 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- FPA 514 and FLA 630 for EDN 12-68 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Fisheye wafer shots for Bender 9/3/68 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Multi-exposure for Lobby display, of computer, Nixies, 727, gal, 5/68 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- LIC Seminar Slides 8/26/68 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- 723 Die & Regulator 7/9/68 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Chicago Spring Conf. booth panels 5/69 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Memory IC chip steps 2/25/69 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Infrared bonder for Bud Oliver 10/8/69 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Model of TO-92 prod. area 12/69 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Fairchild Christmas Card '69 (collateral) 11/69 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Annual Report photos 2/69 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Second Cust. Sat. Poster 5/69 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- "The Word" for letter head 5/9/69 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Hybrid ad photo 2/27/69 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Mary Jane O'brien with stuffed animals pic for field sales 2/28/69 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Diode plant, slides and b&w negs 3/26/69 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Slides and b&w shots of CAD area for Sopkin 11/26/69 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Wescon 1969 Stein's and Steve's shots, etc. 8/69 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- PNP poster thing 10/69 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Three phase temp. control Bob Hood 2/69 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Bob Hood's proposal for anti device to auto makers 6/11/69 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Copy neg of group shot showing Alan Grant and his gen. managers 12/69 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Stein's photo showing people standing above chips 1969 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Stein's shots for art portfolio 1969 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Transparencies from art portfolio 1969 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- MicroPak mailer shots 3/3/69 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Fair. Cam. Stockholder Mtg. 5/69 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Hong Kong pix 1/69 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Eyes for National Sales Conf. logo idea 12/69 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Recruitment brochure 8/69 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Auto ignition module photos for Bob Hood 1969 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- T0-92 test System 1/6/70 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Slides for dice sales promo for Jim Ostendorf 10/70 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Photo showing entire MSI (?) wafer, bright field ilumination 10/70 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- 8 bit A-D conv. on PC board photo for Joel Scheinberg 4/8/70 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- CAD area b&w photos for Fanout 31 6/70 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- 9327 device with Tungsol digivac tubes for Jack Ayre 1/70 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- FT0601 press release photo for J. Ayre 11/70 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Switching transistors for June issue of Distributer Digest 6/70 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Dr. Rupert E. Fixott, dentist, with Explorer Scouts, for John Jollie 5/19/70 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Plastic LIC carrier fortest and shiping, photo for Jack Ayre 7/70 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- FT3903-06 packages for PR 4/13/70 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Viewgraph materials for Martin presentation by Longo & Wells 1/70 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- MEMOS Class. area slides for Maurice O'Shez 10/70 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Pete Portesi at "tube" at R&D 5/70 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Frequency synthesizer using hybrids for FanOut 31 6/4/70 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Annual shareholder's meeting 5/1/70 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Security Analysts meeting 3/31/70 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Bump metalization slides for Dick Wood 10/70 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- CARE program photos for Chicago show for O'brien 5/70 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Some Semiconducter facilities negatives and slides 1970 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Copies of drawings,etc. re: auto stuff for Bob Hood 5/14/70 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- 9341 press release photos for Bill Callahan 4/71 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- FJCC Steering Committee meeting 9/71 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- 9538 press release photos 2/71 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Rex Rice PR photos for Jack Leone 11/71 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Prizes for NOW program + other photos for Now program 5/71 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- uA776 press release photo for Bill Callahan 7/26/71 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Power transistor production line slides for Jim Ostendorf 4/71 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- More auto record photos for Bob Hood 5/71 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Fuel injection module on IH vehicle for Bob Hood 11/71 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Security Analysts meeting 5/11/71 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- MOS packaging shots for Joe Bailey's R&QA brochure 11/71 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Electronic auto equip. slides and b&w photos for Bob Hood 4/71 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Photos for R&QA plastic package brochure, includes testing photos 8/71 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- FSC Shareholders meeting 5/7/71 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Systems conf. slides for Hugh Mays 12/71 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- Plana/Isoplanar slides for Jack Leone, Les Hogan 3/71 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- Slides for Hogan and Downey Paris talks 3/71 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- FAIRLOC gear photo for Roger Borovoy 7/71 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Fire in Plating Shop Photos for Andy Anderson 6/71 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Fire in burn-in oven photos for Andy Anderson 5/71 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- PC board device comparison slides for Norman Doyle presentation 6/71 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- IMS manufacturing slides for Jim Rapaich, IMS Mktg. 7/72 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Dice promo photos for Jim Ostendorf 2/72 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Power headers for Ron Kovacs (0359) TGV 9/72 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Package photos for Gold Plating Book (Ed Duffek) 3/72 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- TTL Data Book cover photo 5/72 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Annual report photos, Most taken by Bill Arbogast others 2/72 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Tad Taguchi photo for INTERNATIONAL INSIGHT 1/72 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Power LIC pkgs & FM Rec. modified by Davis Long, slides 4/72 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Bldg. #6 exterior for Indirect Materials catalogue, Gunther Haller 12/72 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Trans. header shots for Dwight Meadows' Viking program 2/72 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- 2N916 mil. qual. photos for Linda Julian 1/72 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Mil. Qual. for L. Julian 2N1132, 2N1613, 2N2222A 8/72 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- LIC power pkg photos for Pete Rehm 2/72 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Seminex seminar in London for Dave Long 4/72 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- 7750 (contemporar) Shot for Agency 3/72 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Power pkg shots for LIC Eng. - Klaus Koop, Cecilia Thatcher 3/72 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Dist. Mktg. people shots for Rick Martin 8/72 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Demonstration modules for Rodney Smith 10/72 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Hi-Fi reciever with LIC power devices 7/72 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Breadboarded meter circuit using LED's, for Bill Callahan 1/72 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- B&W copy negs from color prints of pkgs for Ed Duffek 4/72 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Analog pres. to TDK Joel Scheinberg and John Husher 3/72 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- 0366 & 0367power header shots for Ron Kovacs 9/72 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- MOD module for Tom Graham, Shiprock plant 7/72 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- MOS Catalogue photos Optimos 7/72 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Walter Burke at NSC, from slide by Doug O'Conner 8/72 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- PPS-25 ROM Simulator Assembly photos for Jim Comstock Ken Crane (builder) 12/13/72 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Chicago booth photos 1972 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Copy neg of four Polaroids showing register diffusions for Bob Waits 12/72 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- IEEE slides for Rob Walker 1/72 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Photos for TLC promotion 6/72 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- FNA-45, LED module copy neg & prints for Callahan 12/72 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- FND 70 SUPERDIGIT, numerical display, b&w copy neg for Bill Callahan 7/72 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- 9344 press release photo for Bill Callahan 1/72 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- 3261 comparison for ED, from Halfon Hamaoui 4/72 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- TGC 0316 Header photos for Ron Kovacs 6/72 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- More power pkg pix for Les Wise 2/72 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Project 2022 components for Frank Perrino 6/72 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- QA Procedure (TO-3) photos for Dave Aven 12/72 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Martin captive line brochure for Duncan Loop 3/72 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Captive line brochure photos for Duncan Loop 2/72 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Semiconductor Progress 9/73 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Various old hybrids for Tony Lopes 12/73 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Transistor packages for Jelen Basford 6/73 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- TGH 0353 & 0319 for Ron Kovacs & George Cashell 6/73 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- 78L Series lead fram for Cecelia Thatcher 9/73 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- 7815 Special #3809 Lead frames for Cecelia Thatcher 9/73 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Mil. Qual. shots for Linda Julian; 2N2219A, 718A, 930, 1132 8/73 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Charge Coupled Device concept slides 4/73 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Unibond slide copies for Alan MacPherson, Corp. Legal 2/73 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- 9720 & 9002 development shots for Heinz Nonnenmacher 5/73 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Stagger lead DIP photos for Bruce Williams 8/73 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- VM 05-TO 220 pkg for Dave Yeaton 3/73 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- TGJ 0351 power transistor header photos for Ron Kovacs 2/73 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Semiconductor Progress Photos for August issue 8/73 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Photos for second issue of Semiconductor Progress 7/73 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- FIFO mailer photo 7/21/73 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Photos for 1st issue of Progress 5/73 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Two PC board photos for app. note 3/29/73 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Thin film machine photos for Glen Possley (Dave Maxwell) 1/73 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Junior Achievement brochure photos for Larry Milstead 1/73 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- More auto slides for Bob Hood 10/22/73 (Box 17, Folder 21)